无需介绍
...no introduction...{
}
名副其实的美国人 人民英雄
and a true American, the people's hero...{
}
“战羊”
Randy "The Ram"...{
}
兰迪·罗宾逊
Robinson!{
}
片名《摔角王》
而战羊旋即起身
And the Ram is up immediately...{
}
俯身冲杀外加一记旋风腿
throwing haymakers and a pile driver!{
}
1984年8月1日 一个值得纪念的夜晚
Here tonight on August 1, 1984-mark it down...{
}
“战羊”兰迪·罗宾逊
Randy "The Ram" Robinson...{
}
18500崇拜者齐集首都
...18,500 fans in the nation's capital.{
}
期望一睹“战羊绝杀”
- They want to see the Ram Jam! - # Well, I'm frustrated #{
}
# And outdated #{
“战羊绝杀”！“战羊绝杀”！
- Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam! - # I really wanna be overrated #{
}
# I'm a finder and I'm a keeper #{
# I'm not a loser I ain't no weeper #{
}
1988年3月23日 “战羊”兰迪·罗宾逊
March 23, 1988, and Randy "The Ram" Robinson...{
}
将与阿亚图拉一决雌雄 （阿亚图拉为伊斯兰领袖之意）
set to do battle with the Ayatollah.{
}
他一定没有预想到自己这一巴掌
... slapping the Ram in his face. He doesn't realize...{
}
将如何激怒“战羊”兰迪·罗宾逊
what this can do to motivate Randy "The Ram" Robinson.{
}
关公面前耍大刀 该出“战羊绝杀”了
Pounding the vice. And it could be time for Ram Jam.{
}
# Bang your head #{
号角吹响了！ 号角吹响了！
- The horns are out! - The horns are out!{
}
# Metal health will drive you mad #{
# Bang your head #{
}
来自中东的阿亚图拉！
... of the Middle East, the Ayatollah!{
}
# Metal health will drive you mad #{
阿亚图拉不会就此罢休的
The Ayatollah will not let go.{
}
他在狠狠教训战羊 天哪！看战羊还能捱多久
He is punishing the Ram. My goodness. How much can this man take?{
}
我们享受过一次又一次的视觉盛宴…
The Ram right where we have seen him so many times before...{
}
又将上演 在这坐满观众的麦迪逊广场花园
playing right to this sold-out Madison Square Garden.{
}
号角吹响了！终于爆发了！ 战羊绝杀！我的天！
The horns are out. Here it comes. Ram Jam! My goodness!{
}
1 2 3…
One, two, three!{
}
结束了 几十年一遇之战
It's over! That's one for the ages.{
}
1989年4月6日
April 6, 1989...{
}
将永久载入职业摔角战史册
will forever go down in professional wrestling history.{
}
（20年之后）
表演很精彩 战羊
Great show, Ram.{
}
你真把他们唬住了
You really put them over.{
}
这给你
Here you go.{
}
对不起 我以为会有更多观众的
Sorry. I was sure the gate'd be bigger.{
}
不过别忘了 两个月之后 在纳维有个签名会
But don't forget. Two months. Rahway. Legend signing.{
}
我可指望你了 老兄
I need you, man.{
}
嘿 战羊
Yo, Ram.{
}
能给我签个名吗？
Think you could, uh, sign this for me?{
}
- 当然 - 多谢 老兄
- Sure. - Thanks a lot, man.{
}
我有生以来看的第一场摔角赛 就是你在圣殿打戴维.戴蒙的那场
My first match ever was you versus Davey Diamond at the Spectrum.{
}
- 多谢 - 哦 是啊
- Thanks a lot. - Oh, yeah.{
}
- 1985年 - 那场打的不错
- 1985. - That was a good one.{
}
没错 你帅呆了
Yeah. You were awesome.{
}
- 心领了 老兄 给你 - 多谢 多谢 战羊
- Appreciate it, bro. There you go. - Thanks. Thanks, Ram.{
}
他人不错
Nice guy, don't you think?{
}
# Over, baby #{
# Take some time Let me know #{
}
# If you really want to go #{
# Don't know what you got till it's #{
}
妈的！
Oh, shit.{
}
蓝利
Lenny.{
}
蓝利
Lenny.{
}
拜托了 蓝利 开开门
Come on, Lenny. Open up.{
}
我靠哦 蓝利
Goddamn it, Lenny.{
}
靠
Fuck.{
}
我操！
Fuck.{
}
- 战羊！ - 快醒来啊！战羊！
- Ram! - Wake up! Ram!{
}
- 战羊！ - 快起来吧 战羊！
- Ram! - Come on! Ram! Wake up!{
}
- 开门！ - 战羊！
- Open up! - Ram!{
}
快起来！
- Wake up! - Wake up! Wake up!{
}
- 战羊！ - 醒醒！
- Ram! - Wake up!{
}
是谁在吵我？
Who woke me up?{
}
冲喉一掷！
Choke slam!{
}
- 再来一个！ - 再来一次 战羊！
- One more! - Come on, Ram!{
}
一会儿再来找你们这群疯猴子
I'll see you maniacs in a little while.{
}
- 说好了 我一会儿回来 - 来一个战羊绝杀！
- All right? I'll be back. - Aw! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
等我回来
I'll be back.{
}
- 不会走远的 - 战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
- I ain't going anyplace. - Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
- 蓝利 - 嗯？
- Lenny. - Yeah.{
}
蓝利 为什么做的这么绝？
Lenny, why are you doing this to me?{
}
- 不交钱 就别想进门 - 哎 别这样 蓝利
- You'll get in when I get my money. - Aw, come on, Lenny.{
}
你知道我不抵赖房钱的
You know I'm always good for it.{
}
没错 欠账的时候你才想起交钱的
Yeah, you're always good for it every time this happens.{
}
拜托了 老兄 我的背又痛了 至少让我回去拿一下我的冰敷袋阿
Come on, brother. My back went out. Let me just at least get my ice packs.{
}
- 我可帮不了你 - 拜托了 大哥
- I cannot help you. - Come on, man.{
}
哦 老天
Oh, God.{
}
你需不需要低卡高蛋白的？
Do you need extra protein without the extra calories?{
}
请到前面 谢谢
... to the front, please.{
}
嗨 拉法尔
Hey, Rafael!{
}
- 嗨 伟恩 方便聊两句吗？ - 不怎么方便 怎么了？
- Hey, Wayne, you got a second? - Not really. Why?{
}
嗯 你能不能让我多干几个小时？
Well, I was wondering if you could throw me some more hours.{
}
怎么了？绷腿带涨价了？（摔角用的绷腿带）
What's the matter? Did they raise the price of tights?{
}
呵呵…
Funny.{
}
我看看轮班表
Let's see what we got.{
}
工作日行吗 周日我比较忙
Weekdays. I'm busy on the weekends.{
}
- 你认识他们吧 - 怎么样 兰迪？
- You know the boys. - What's up, Ram?{
}
- 嘿嘿 怎么样 - 高兴见到你
- Hey. What's up? - Good to see you.{
}
嘿 老兄 你看起来状态威猛哦 混得怎么样
Hey, bro. Look at you. You're all diesel, man. How you doing, brother?{
}
- 真高兴见到你 兄弟 - 好了 就在这换吧
- Good to see you, man. - Okay. Right here, you can change.{
}
- 好的 - 给我钱
- All right, man. - I want my money.{
}
给你
There you go.{
}
好了 伙计们 听着
All right, guys. Listen up.{
}
SLG 你在哪呢
All right. S.L.G., where are you?{
}
- 你第一个上场 打TDS - 谢谢
- You're up first against T.D.S. - Thank you.{
}
第二组 哈沃和科本打比利和列克斯
Second, we got Havoc and Cobian versus Billy the Kid and Lex Lethal.{
}
- 嘿 我今晚跟你打 - 第三组 萨班打德温
- Yo, I got you tonight. - Third, Sabian versus Devon Moore.{
}
第四组 犹德斯打罗伯 接着中场休息
Fourth, Judas the Traitor versus Rob Eckos. Intermission.{
}
第五组 凯文马修斯打“人间地狱”
Fifth, Kevin Matthews versus Inferno.{
}
第六组 苏格和DJ海德打“出格”萨莫斯
Sixth, we got Sugga and DJ Hyde versus the Funky Samoans.{
}
第七组 保罗和安迪打吉姆和帕帕顿
Seventh, Paul E. Normous and Andy Anderson versus Jim Powers and Papadon.{
}
最后压轴的
And last but not least, for the strap...{
}
汤米·罗敦打“战羊”兰迪·罗宾逊
we got Tommy Rotten versus Randy the Ram.{
}
好了 都听到了？
All right. You guys got it?{
}
是 明白了
- Yep. - Got it.{
}
- 好了 开工吧 大家玩得愉快 - 好的
- All right. Let's do this. Have a good time. - All right.{
}
嘿 战羊
Hey, Ram.{
}
哎 怎么样 老弟
Hey, there. How you doing, man?{
}
咳 汤米 今晚咱俩一组
Hey. Tommy. We're gonna be working tonight.{
}
我记得你 汤米 两个月前在宾夕法尼亚见过你打
I know you, Tommy. I saw you out in, uh, Pennsylvania a couple months ago.{
}
- 艾伦镇 - 你打得很赞！很有功力
- Allentown. - You were really good. You really brought it.{
}
- 谢谢 谢谢 - 继续努力 老弟
- Thank you. Thank you. - Keep working, man.{
}
你知道 开卡迪拉克的人
You know, people who drive the Cadillacs...{
}
他们说了算 他们是老板
the ones with the politics...they run the show.{
}
- 跟打得好不好无关 只要你坚持 就有出头日 - 是 我知道
- It ain't about ability, so you just hang in there. - Yeah, I know, I know.{
}
- 那就好 - 不过说回来 今晚…
- All right. - But, uh, as far as tonight...{
}
你打算怎么打？
I don't know what you wanna do.{
}
我有个想法 为了场面火爆一些
I had a few ideas. I was thinking, you know, maybe just for the heat...{
}
- 我打你一个低拳 接着灌头 - 稍稍炒一下就好了 老弟
- I would give you a low blow, follow it up with a bulldog. - Just bring the cheap heat, bro.{
}
- 你们狠狠给我们热场 - 好
- You guys should get the heat on us right away. - All right.{
}
狠狠打我们 越狠越好
Keep the heat on us, beat the shit out of us. Boom, boom, boom, boom.{
}
我们会上栏绳
We'll come up, we'll get on the ropes.{
}
- 你们把我们俩狠狠打下来 - 好
- You guys bring us both in the hard way. - Okay.{
}
我们起身 两脚踢 重砸在场上
Then we get up, double dropkick, we powder out again.{
}
好吧 我们今晚好好秀一场
All right. So we're gonna really milk it tonight.{
}
- 尽情秀一场 不紧不慢 保守一点 - 走保守派
- We're gonna milk it. Nice and slow, old-school, easy. - Old...school.{
}
别往腿上使劲了,老兄 老掉牙的套式
Don't work his leg, man. That's...Everybody does that.{
}
- 打脖子 - 不行 不行 我们这组打脖子
- Work his neck. Work his neck. - No, no. We working the neck.{
}
- 你们打脖子？ - 我们打腿
- You're working the neck? - I already got the leg.{
}
- 你们打腿？ - 脖子还是腿？
- All right. You guys got the leg? - Leg or neck. What you got?{
}
- 我看你可以从那开始回击 - 从拦绳跳下来回击？
- Maybe make your comeback right off there. - Bang off the ropes...{
}
狠灌一腿 然后“战羊绝杀
then super kick and, uh, Ram Jam...{
}
完事之后咱们去喝一杯 怎么样？
and we go have a beer, okay?{
}
- 好主意 老兄 - 你好好坚持下去 你有潜力
- That sounds great, man. - You hang in there. You got a lot of ability.{
}
- 好的 好的 - 明白？
- All right. All right. - Okay?{
}
- 明白 - 谢谢
- Right. - Thank you.{
}
保佑你
Bless you.{
}
”战羊“兰迪·罗宾逊
... Randy "The Ram" Robinson!{
}
嘿 上场吧！战羊！ 就看你的了！
Yeah! Come on, Ram! You're the man!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
上场！上场！
Come on! Come on!{
}
没事吧 战羊？
You all right, Ram?{
}
兰迪 你还好吧？
Ram, you all right?{
}
- 我要把他的手臂撕了！ - 需要我叫停吗？
- I'm gonna rip his arm off! - You want me to stop it?{
}
- 看他能不能行 裁判 - 需要我叫停吗？
- Check him, ref! - You want me to stop it?{
}
你肯定？
Are you sure?{
}
起来
Come on.{
}
嘘我？给你们点好看的！
I'll give you something to boo about!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
- Ram Jam! Ram Jam! - Yeah!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
你好烂！你还是好烂！
You still suck! You still suck!{
}
你好烂！你还是好烂！
You still suck! You still suck!{
}
你好烂！你还是好烂！
You still suck! You still suck!{
}
加油！起来！
Come on! Get up!{
}
你们见识到了吧？
Is that what you want to see?{
}
过来 你这肥猪！
Come here, you fat piece of crap!{
}
滚到台下去吧
Get out there with the rest of the party!{
}
等我下去 把你们一个个打趴下！
I'm coming out there, and I'll beat the hell out of each and every one of you!{
}
你们以为你们嘘谁呢？ 等我下去暴虐你们一顿！
You know who you're dealing with? I will destroy you people!{
}
给我闭嘴！ 死期到了 老不死的！
Shut the hell up! That's it, old man!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
1 2 3…
One, two, three!{
}
先生们女士们 我们的获胜者就是…
Ladies and gentlemen, here is your winner...{
}
”战羊“兰迪·罗宾逊
Randy "The Ram" Robinson!{
}
兰迪 你真是把观众制伏了
Ram, you really popped that crowd.{
}
- 我把伤口包一下 行吗？ - 行
- I'm just gonna glue this up, okay? - Yep.{
}
嘿 兰迪 有时间聊两句？
Yo, Ram, you got a sec?{
}
进来
Come on in.{
}
有个大日子就快到了 你记得吗？
You realize what's coming up?{
}
-  啊？ - 4月6日
- Huh? - April 6.{
}
你跟阿亚图拉在麦迪逊广场花园绝战 20周年纪念日
Twentieth anniversary of you and Ayatollah at the Garden.{
}
我知道 嗯…
- I know. Hey. Mm-hmm. - Yeah.{
}
- 真是好久以前了 - 一眨眼工夫 不是吗？
- Long time ago. - Time fucking flies, right?{
}
我脑子里有两个字
Here's what I'm thinkin'{
}
重战
Two words: Re... match.{
}
好了 兰迪 包好了
Okay, Ram. You're all set.{
}
到时候我们会在惠灵顿搞个盛大的特别活动 要颁发”荣誉腰带“的
We're doing this big Fanfest thing down in Wilmington with Ring of Honor that weekend.{
}
我想让你们俩压轴
I wanna main event it with you two guys.{
}
"战羊对决阿亚图拉 世纪II战"
"Ram, Ayatollah II."{
}
我听说鲍勃在亚利桑那 卖二手车干的很不错
Hey. I heard Bob was doing really good with his used car lot out in Arizona.{
}
- 我不肯定他会不会… - 拜托 为了这个…
- I don't know if he's gonna-You know. - Come on. For this?{
}
鲍勃会把尘封的包头布再找出来的 （伊斯兰头布 意指会复出）
Bob's gonna dust off the old turban.{
}
- 真的？ - 真的
- Yeah? - Yeah.{
}
- 好 说定了 - 行
- Hey, bring it. - Okay.{
}
- 为战羊！ - 战羊！
- That's for Ram! - Ram!{
}
- 打得好！打得好！ - 威风不减当年！
- Good stuff. Good stuff. - Good stuff. Just like the old days.{
}
来吧 兄弟们！ 大家一起洗澡去！
Come on, guys. Let's all go take a shower together.{
}
怎么样 战羊？ 一切还好吧？
What's up, Ram? How you doing?{
}
-你怎么样 大个子克里斯？ - 我还好
- What's up, Big Chris? What's shaking? - I'm all right.{
}
你跟健身房那药贩子还联系么？
Yo, baby, you still got that hookup with that quack at your gym? The juice head?{
}
- 你怎么了？ - 我的背疼死了
- What do you need? - Yo, my back is killing me.{
}
去痛片或者麻醉药 随便哪个
Vicodin, Perc, Nubain, whatever he's got.{
}
- 过几天来打馆找我吧 包在我身上 - 还是你行 战羊！你真行！
- Come by the mansion in a couple of days, I'll hook you up. - You the man, Ram. You the man.{
}
- 嘿 鲁比宝贝 近来可好？ - 嘿 战羊 你好啊
- Hey, Ruby. How you doing, baby? - Hey, Ram. How's it goin'{
}
- 我要杯凉的 - 好的
- I'll take a cold one. - All right.{
}
给你
There you go.{
}
- 卡斯蒂在吗？ - 她应该在包房里
- Cassidy around? - I think she's working the V.I.P.{
}
哦 谢谢
Yeah, thank you.{
}
# I got a question, if you can answer this #{
# I got a question #{
}
听我的 宝贝 我保证你爽歪歪
Trust me, baby. You're gonna be so happy.{
}
抱歉 美女 不过我们点的是另一个妞
I'm sorry, sweetie. We said the other girl.{
}
那个金发妞 挂脐环的 另一个妞
Yeah, the blonde girl with the belly chain. Yeah, the other girl.{
}
- 哦 不过她现在休息 - 抱歉 宝贝 不过我们真的没点你
- Well, yeah, but she's on break. - I'm sorry, but we really don't want you.{
}
- 你今年几岁了？ - 你看起来跟我妈差不多大
- How old are you anyway? - Oh, you're like my mom's age.{
}
靠的就是经验知道么？
Hey. There's nothing like experience.{
}
我干得了的事 你未婚妻想都想不到
I do things your fiance's never even dreamed of doing.{
}
呵呵 比如你25年前毕业离校…
Yeah, like graduate in 1985!{
}
嘿 你俩小屁孩该对女士尊重些
Hey, hey. You girls are being a little rude to the lady.{
}
- 我看你们得道个歉 - 你他妈的哪根葱？
- How about an apology? - Who the fuck are you, man?{
}
别这样跟女士说话
Don't talk to the lady like that.{
}
- 我想怎么说就怎么说 - 没事 多谢你
- I'll talk to her like I wanna talk to her. - No, it's okay. Thanks.{
}
- 你用不着那样对她说话 - 没事没事
- You don't need to be talking to her like that. - It's cool. I got it.{
}
- 我明白了 没事 伙计们 - 不 我来告诉你
- I got it. It's all right, guys. - No. Let me tell you something.{
}
我可以跟你们保证 这位女士 比你要娶的
I guarantee you, this lady's a hundred times hotter...{
}
烂货婊子要辣100倍
than any skank-ass pussy you're gonna be marrying.{
}
- 你说什么屁话！那是我姐姐！ - 你说什么？
- What the fuck? That's my fucking sister. - What you say?{
}
你他妈的有没搞错？
Are you fucking kidding me? Are you kidding me?{
}
- 操蛋 - 回见
- Fucker. - See you soon.{
}
他妈的200块就这么给你轰走了
200 fuckin' bucks walked out.{
}
哎 我是想帮你
Hey, I'm just trying to help.{
}
哎 拜托 他们都是混蛋
Oh, come on. They were punks.{
}
- 你！ - 哎 别激动
- You! - Hey. Whoa. Easy there.{
}
对不起
I'm sorry.{
}
再说了 我比他们都好看
I'm better-looking than them anyway.{
}
我没打算惹你生气 别这样
I didn't mean to piss you off. Come on.{
}
嗯？好吧…
Yeah? Okay.{
}
- 真高兴见到你 兰迪 - 见到你真好 老天爷
- It's good to see you, Ram. - Good to see you. Goddamn.{
}
有一阵子没见你了 过得怎么样？
I haven't seen you in a while. How you been?{
}
你听好了 那可是载入史册一战
Now, I'm telling you, it was one of the historic matches in history.{
}
2万人观战
It was 20,000 people.{
}
另外还有150万人在家付费观看
Another million and a half sitting at home watching it on pay-per-view.{
}
我们打得如火如荼
We're slamming the piss out of each other.{
}
持久战 都不知道打了多久
I mean, for God knows how long. We're both gassing.{
}
随便问一个摔角迷 无人不晓
You ask any wrestling fan, they've heard about that one.{
}
- 150万人 老天 - 哦 是阿 大件事来的
- Million and a half. Shit. - Oh, yeah, it was big.{
}
重战 意味着历史重演
And a rematch? Hey. This could be history all over again.{
}
老天爷 看你 真是惹火的尤物阿
Goddamn, look at you. You are one smoking baby. Mmm.{
}
不如嫁给我吧？
Let me make an honest woman out of you.{
}
以后的事情谁知道呢 至少我现在还很有型
I mean, who knows? I'm in pretty good shape right now.{
}
要知道 如果运气好的话 我可能就借这机会重振雄风了
You know, with a little luck, this could be my ticket back on top.{
}
- 人才需要机遇 - 对阿对阿
- You never know who's in that crowd. - Yeah. Yeah.{
}
希望不只是一场梦
That would be a dream.{
}
哦 老天 你在流血
Oh, Jesus. You're bleeding.{
}
呵呵 今晚割的
- Oh! - Yeah, I got cut tonight.{
}
- 你没事吧？ - 嗯 没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah, it's nothin'{
}
- 他们说摔角都是假摔 对吧？ - 假摔？我给你见识一下这所谓的“假摔”
- They say wrestling's fake, huh? - Fake? I'll show you fake.{
}
这个是1986年在丹佛体育场
Look at this. 1986, Denver Coliseum.{
}
比利 鲍勃 班鸠 一块大木板劈下来
Billy Bob Banjo hit me with a two-by-four.{
}
木板上还有铁钉 当即把我的二头肌劈的开花
It had a loose nail in it, split my bicep right the hell open.{
}
这个 更凶悍
- Mmm. Mmm. - Look at that. I got a better one than that.{
}
看这里
Take a look at this here.{
}
1988年在奥兰多市民中心
1988, okay? Orlando Civic Center.{
}
“无与伦比先生”把我扔上栏绳
Mr. Magnificent threw me over the top ropes.{
}
我肩膀着地 把锁骨摔了个两半
I landed on my shoulder and cracked my clavicle right in half.{
}
哦 老天爷 疼不疼啊？
Oh, my God. Does it hurt?{
}
嗯 我呼吸的时候很疼 不过 我也听到观众的狂吼
Well, it hurts when I breathe, but, I mean, you know, you hear the roar of the crowd...{
}
那样的时候 你只有顶住 撑过去
you just- you motor through, you know?{
}
"他因四条罪责被钉在十字架上“
"He was pierced for our transgressions.{
}
"他粉碎于我们的罪孽”
"He was crushed for our iniquities.{
}
”因他之受罚 我们终获和平“
"The punishment that brought us peace was upon him...{
}
“因他之所伤 我们终获治愈"
and by his wounds we were healed."{
}
嗯 这都是什么乱七八糟的
Hmm. What was that all about?{
}
是”耶稣受难记“台词阿 你的头发跟他很像
It's The Passion of the Christ. You have the same hair.{
}
- 你没看过？ - 没有
- You never seen it? - No.{
}
大哥！你一定要看 不可错过
Dude, you gotta! It's...It's amazing.{
}
他们朝他扔鞭子 石头 箭头…
- They throw everything at him- whips, arrows, rocks. - Hmm.{
}
他们打他整整两个小时 打得他死去活来
They beat the living fuck out of him the whole two hours, and...{
}
他只是默默承受
- he just takes it. - Hmm.{
}
硬汉一条
Tough dude.{
}
自我牺牲的战羊
Sacrificial Ram.{
}
下一个上台的是 卡斯蒂
Next on the main stage will be Cassidy-{
}
小舞台上另有伴舞
with Harmony on the small stage.{
}
噢 靠
Aw, fuck.{
}
- 我得走了 - 你去哪？
- Gotta go. - Where you going?{
}
我欠你多少钱？
What do I owe ya?{
}
- 六十块 - 六十块
- That's 60. - Sixty.{
}
- 不用找了 - 谢谢
- Keep the change. - Thank you.{
}
鬼老天！
Goddamn.{
}
将要闪亮登场的是 热辣的卡斯蒂
... to the stage, the lovely Cassidy!{
}
# Don't throw it all away #{
# Baby #{
}
# I'm beggin'you, please #{
# Don't walk away #{
}
一瓶安那达尔（激素） 250块 一瓶EQ 75块
Bottle of Anadrol, 250. Bottle of E.Q., 75 bucks.{
}
两瓶特朗 75块一瓶
Two bottles of tren, $75 each...a buck, 50.{
}
一瓶胰岛素 100块 还有四瓶睾丸酮
Bottle of insulin, 100 bucks. You got four boxes of Sustanon.{
}
一盒三支 30块
There's three amps in a box, $30 on a box- a buck, 20.{
}
一瓶大力补 100块 还有你的大咪咪 我准备了瑞宁德 200块
A bottle of DBOL, 100 bucks. For your bitch tits, I got you a bottle of Arimidex, 200 bucks.{
}
总共995块钱 我知道你只有400块 都给我好了
All together, 995. I know you only got 400. Give me the 400.{
}
- 我知道你不会赖账的 - 有没有GHB？（类似酒精的药 又称迷魂水）
- I know you're good for the rest. - Got any G.H.?{
}
中国人卖那个 不过我有雪兰思定
Got Chinese and I got Serostim.{
}
我可不要那中国货
I don't want any of that Chinese stuff.{
}
你真是没让我失望 战羊
You're my boy, Ram.{
}
- 我会帮你搞定 - 好的
- I'll hook you up, all right? - Okay.{
}
你得把制菌剂一起用上
You gotta take the bacteriostatic water with it too.{
}
它能让肌肉长得更持久
It makes the growth last longer. Need anything else?{
}
去痛片之类？“维克”还是“帕克”？（去痛片名称）
Painkillers? Vics? Percs?{
}
- 不用了 兄弟 我手头很紧 - 德美罗？（止痛药）
- No, bro. I'm tapped. - Demerol?{
}
- 盐酸氧可酮？（另一种止痛药）确定什么都不用？ - 不用了 这个可以了
- OxyContins? You sure? - No, this'll do me.{
}
- 伟哥？或者来点大麻？ - 不用
- Viagra? Maybe some blow? - No.{
}
- 我这里应有尽有 只要你需要 尽管说 - 我看你可以开药店了 老哥
- Got it all, man. Whatever you need, you know. - Opened up a pharmacy, brother.{
}
- 你是我兄弟 我当然要罩着你 - 我就需要这些了
- You're my man. I gotta look out for you. - Yeah, I'm square.{
}
就要些药水 对吧？
Just need the juice, and you're all right, then, right?{
}
- 我就是想多长点肌肉 - 是阿 你练得不错 兄弟
- I'm just gonna get big and strong. - Yes, you are, my friend.{
}
- 好的 - 随时找我 兄弟
- Okay. - All right? Anytime, man.{
}
- 你现在状态很好 大哥 - 尽量保持 尽量
- You're looking good, brother. - I'm trying, baby. I'm trying.{
}
- 秀给我看看 - 阿 来吧 来吧
- Show me what you got there. - Ah, come on, man. Come on.{
}
- 让我看看你的成果 - 不算什么啦 没什么大头的
- Show me what you got. - Just a little something. There's not much there, baby.{
}
- 来吧 - 吹起来 吹起来 看看这家伙
- Come on. - Bring it up. Bring it up. Look at that motherfucker.{
}
就这里 就是这里了
- Okay, right up there. See? What you're doing right there. - Mm-hmm.{
}
别让锡纸留太久 因为上次染的时候 锡纸破了
Don't...Don't leave the foils on too long, because last time they broke off.{
}
时间过长 可能焦了
I think they got too fried.{
}
好 知道了
Yeah. I got it.{
}
你老头子现在怎么样？
So, how's the old man doing these days?{
}
- 工作 工作 工作 - 工作 工作 工作…
- Work, work, work. - Work, work, work. Well, hey.{
}
至少他有工可做对吧？
Hmm. At least he's got a job, right?{
}
- 嘿 格洛丽亚 近来可好？ - 嘿 宝贝 5号房可以用
- Hey, Gloria. How you doin' - Hey, babe. Five's open.{
}
- 多谢你载我 老兄 - 客气
- Thanks again for the lift, bro. - You got it.{
}
放马过来吧 打这里 尽管打
Here you go. Lay it on, brother. Lay it on.{
}
这样…
- Like...Like... - There you go.{
}
你怎么没有双膝跪倒？
You're supposed to fall to your knees.{
}
- 哦 - 很好
- Ooh. - All right. Good.{
}
- 灭虫剂在哪？ - 六号通道右手边
- Where's the bug spray in here? Huh? - Lane six on the right side.{
}
- 右手边 最后面 - 右手 灭虫剂
- The right side, bottom. - Right side, bug spray.{
}
再来
- Hmm? - Go ahead. Once more.{
}
- 现在轮到我了 - 好吧
- Now give it to me, brother. - All right, man.{
}
靠哦 加把劲…
Fuck. Come on. Let's...{
}
- 买两个灭鼠器？ - 装上 放好 等着好戏
- Couple mousetraps? - Load 'em and set 'em in the ring, body slam.{
}
嗯 就这么干
Hmm. Let's do it.{
}
- 你好啊 长官？ - 你好
- How you doing, sir? - How you doing?{
}
有什么事吗 兄弟？
What's going on, my man?{
}
看看这个怎么样？酷不酷
Tell me, what do you think? What do you think about this?{
}
阿？
Huh?{
}
- 我看行 - 好吧
- That'll work. - Okay.{
}
过来
Come here.{
}
- 我看起来还不怎么样 不过我感觉很好噢 - 嗯
- I don't look good, but I feel good. - Yeah.{
}
膝盖 背 你说怎么打 咱就怎么打 大哥
So, my...my knees, my back, anything you need me to do, sir.{
}
只要跑动少一些就行
Just maybe, uh, keep the running to a minimum.{
}
你把我踢上拦绳 你狠砸我
Like maybe I can hit the ropes once, take a bump for you,{
}
不过拜托 别打大十字
but, like, no crisscrossing, please.{
}
关于压轴的套路 你说说
This hard-core stuff. What do you-Talk to me about it.{
}
你打算我们怎么打？
What do you wanna do tonight?{
}
嗯 你能扛得住订书机吗？
Well, are you cool with the staples?{
}
- 订书机？ - 往你身上订那种
- Staples? - Staple gun.{
}
- 什么意思？ - 往身上订钉子的枪之类…
- What do you mean? - Like... staple gun.{
}
- 订书枪 - 对 你过去从来没试过？
- Staple gun. - Yeah. You never did it before?{
}
- 没有 疼不疼？ - 近乎白痴问法 当然疼
- Uh, no. Does that hurt? - Silly question, but yeah.{
}
大哥 打进去的时候倒不算疼
- Man, uh, not so bad going in. - Yeah.{
}
不过看着吓人 你想想 那么个金属枪直愣愣对着…
Kind of scary. You know, you got a big metal thing up against you, but...{
}
拔出来的时候 身上会有钉孔 流点血
pulling them out, they're gonna leave a couple little holes, a little bit of blood loss there.{
}
- 放马过来吧 - 谢谢 大哥 真是我的荣幸 谢谢
- Rock and roll. - Thank you, sir. It's an honor. Thank you.{
}
- 尽管使订书枪吧 - 好的 大哥
- Take it easy with that staple gun. - No problem, sir.{
}
你死定了！
Dead! You're so dead!{
}
你死定了！
You're so dead! You're so dead!{
}
你死定了！
You're so dead! You're so dead!{
}
你死定了！
You're so dead! You're so dead!{
}
1 2 3…
One, two, three!{
}
女士们先生们 今晚的冠军就是…
Ladies and gentlemen, your winner, the legend...{
}
传奇“战羊”兰迪·罗宾逊
Randy "The Ram" Robinson!{
}
# Bang your head #{
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
太精彩了 战羊！
Great show, Ram.{
}
干的漂亮！
Great job.{
}
他来了
There he is.{
}
炼狱式的一仗！很精彩！
Hell of a match out there, man. Hell of a match.{
}
- 谢谢 - 简直是舍身一战啊兄弟 太出色了
- Thank you. - Put yourself through hell, man. Great. Good work. Way to go.{
}
- 简直是不要命的 战羊 - 我先包扎下
- It was fucking insane, Ram. - Let me just get some glue for that.{
}
太疯狂了
Crazy shit, man. Crazy.{
}
哎 桌板砸你不轻 你还好吧？
Hey. You okay with that table hit?{
}
- 死不了 大哥 死不了 - 那就好
- I'll live, sir. I'll live. - Yeah. Okay.{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
靠
Ah, shit.{
}
- 这么多订书钉 得取出来 - 没大碍的 别太着紧 大夫
- Got a lot of staples. We gotta take 'em out. - Fuck it. Take it easy, Doc.{
}
顶住
- Hold still. - Ow!{
}
操哦！
Goddamn it.{
}
你这变态G8！
You sick fuck! You sick fuck!{
}
你这变态G8！
You sick fuck!{
}
你这变态G8！
You sick fuck!{
}
你这变态G8！
You sick fuck! You sick fuck!{
}
刀叉伺候！
It's dinnertime!{
}
操了！
Oh, fuck!{
}
老天！
Goddamn it!{
}
漂亮！打！
Yeah! Yeah! Hit him!{
}
干掉他！
Yeah, get him!{
}
- 战羊！ - 用他的假肢！
- Ram! - Yeah! Use his leg!{
}
战羊！用我的假肢！ 用我的假肢！
Ram, use my leg! Use it! Use my leg!{
}
用吧！用吧！
Use his leg! Use his leg!{
}
- 求你了 用我的假肢扁他！ - 用吧！用吧！
- Come on! Use my leg! - Use his leg! Use his leg!{
}
用吧！用吧！
- Yeah! Yeah! - Use his leg! Use his leg!{
}
用他的假肢！用他的假肢！
Use his leg! Use his leg!{
}
用他的假肢！
Use his leg! Use his leg!{
}
操你哦！操你他妈的！
Fuck you, Necro! Fuck you!{
}
我得把这个取出来
Okay. Let me get this out.{
}
扎得比较深
This is in there pretty good, Ram.{
}
我要干掉他！
I'm gonna kill him!{
}
- 你没事吧？ - 嗯
- You're good? - Yeah.{
}
就快好了
I'm almost done.{
}
见鬼去吧！尼克罗！
Fuck you, Necro!{
}
见鬼去！
Fuck you, Necro!{
}
你会死的很难看！死的很难看！
You're so dead! You're so dead!{
}
死定了你！死定了！
You're so dead! You're so dead!{
}
弄好了 战羊 去洗个澡吧
Okay, Ram. You're good. Go take a shower.{
}
干的漂亮 战羊
Good work, man.{
}
我们按计划完成的不错
I think we did what we wanted to do.{
}
不 第一次表现是…
No, first time, coming off...{
}
方式重复了
Way over.{
}
战羊！
Ram. Ram!{
}
放松 尽量放松
Try and relax. Just try and relax.{
}
梅林 能帮个手吗
Marlene, can I have some help in here, please?{
}
把手放下 尽量放松就好 冷静
Put your arms down. Okay, try and relax. Calm down.{
}
放松
Okay, just relax.{
}
很好 很好 冷静
Okay. Very good. Okay. Calm down.{
}
- 好了 谢谢你 梅林 - 没事
- Okay. Thanks, Marlene. - Okay.{
}
- 操 - 兰姆斯基先生？
- Ah, fuck. - Mr. Ramzinski?{
}
叫我兰迪就好
Call me Randy.{
}
兰迪 我是毛也迪扎医生
Randy, I'm Dr. Moayedizadeh.{
}
我现在怎么样？
So, how's it all looking?{
}
嗯 比心脏桥接手术之前强多了
Well, much better than before the bypass.{
}
那就是说 我没事？ 什么也不用担心？
Oh. So, we're in the clear? We're all good?{
}
嗯 这心脏是你的
Well, it's your heart.{
}
你得学着好好照顾它
You need to start taking better care of it.{
}
怎么照顾？
Like how? What do I do?{
}
首先 你得开始服用大量药物
Well, for starters, you're going to be on a slew of medications.{
}
还有你得停止吃那些增强肌肉和力量的激素
And the stuff that you're putting in your body...you need to cut it out.{
}
我知道 我可以…
I know. I know. I can...{
}
不用吃激素我也没问题
I can...I can do without that.{
}
我什么时候可以重新健身
When can I, uh, get back in the gym and, uh...{
}
为摔角作准备？
start working out?{
}
如果你想继续健身 没问题 只要不过度过量
As far as exercise goes, it's still okay, as long as it's moderate.{
}
大夫 我是职业摔角选手
Doc, I'm a professional wrestler.{
}
那恐怕不行
That's not a good idea.{
}
嗯 怎么说？
Well, what do you mean?{
}
你的心脏已经超负荷
Well, your heart has been through a lot.{
}
它无法承受大量过激运动
It won't be able to handle a strenuous activity.{
}
嗯 我可以放缓训练以及摔角 我可以自己控制节奏
Well, I can slow my routine down. I can...I can just pace myself.{
}
- 兰姆斯基先生… - 兰迪 叫我兰迪
- Mr. Ramzinski... - Randy. Call me Randy.{
}
兰迪 你差点连命都没了
Randy, you almost died.{
}
下次可能就没这么幸运了
Next time, you might not be so lucky.{
}
呵呵 大夫
Well, hey, Doc.{
}
感谢你给我带来的好消息咯
Thanks for all the good news.{
}
这份给你
This copy's for you.{
}
有人留了这个给你
And somebody left this for you.{
}
他自称你的赞助人
He said he was your promoter.{
}
罗宾·兰姆斯基 请到药房来
Robin Ramzinski, come to the pharmacy.{
}
你的处方药开好了
- Your prescription's ready. - Oh.{
}
- 罗宾·兰姆斯基？ - 兰迪
- Robin Ramzinski? - Randy.{
}
请在这儿签名
Just sign here, please.{
}
谢谢
Thank you.{
}
给你
Here you go.{
}
我的钱
My money.{
}
1 2 3 4 5…
One, two, three, four, five...{
}
欢迎回来
Welcome home.{
}
啊 操了…
Oh, shit.{
}
嘿 亚当！
Hey, Adam!{
}
- 要不要玩游戏机？ - 好吧
- You wanna play Nintendo? - All right.{
}
让我看看你水平如何
Okay. Let's see what you got there.{
}
- 阿亚图拉出来了 - 好怕怕哦
- All right. Here comes the Ayatollah. - Shaking in my boots.{
}
- 准备开始 - 你听说过《使命召唤4》吗？
- Here we go. Come on. - So, you hear about Call of Duty 4?{
}
什么？
Did I what?{
}
- 使命召唤4 - 什么？
- Call of Duty 4? - What?{
}
- 使命召唤4 - 叫它使命4？
- Call of Duty 4. - Call "It" Duty 4?{
}
- 使命召唤4 - 使命召唤4？
- Call of Duty 4. - Call of Duty 4?{
}
- 有点酷毙了 - 真的？
- Yeah. It's pretty cool, actually. - Really?{
}
你这个游戏太老掉牙了
This game is so old.{
}
- 那是什么游戏？ - 战斗游戏 还有其他使命召唤游戏
- Wh...What's it about? - It's a war game. Most all the other Call of Duties...{
}
都是打二战的 不过这个是关于伊拉克
they were, like, based on World War II, but this one's with Iraq.{
}
- 哦 是吗？ - 嗯
- Oh, yeah? - And-Yeah.{
}
你可以角色转换 可以当水兵
You switch off between a Marine...{
}
或者当“S” 英国特工
and an "S" and "S" British special operative...{
}
- 真的很酷 - 哇
- so it's pretty cool. - Wow.{
}
顶住 顶住 这就对了
Hold on. All right. Hold on. There we go.{
}
没错 就这里！战羊绝杀 搞定
All right. Here- There! There it is! Ram Jam! You're finished.{
}
- 再玩一局 - 我得走了
- Okay, one more. - I gotta go.{
}
- 阿？ - 我得走了
- Huh? - I...I gotta leave.{
}
- 我刚把你打的屁滚尿流 你不想扳回来？ - 不用啦 没所谓
- I just gave you an ass-whipping. Don't you wanna get even? - Nah, that's okay.{
}
- 好吧 - 我过阵子再来找你 哈？
- All right. - I...I'll catch you later, all right?{
}
好吧 回见
All right. See you later, man.{
}
- 记得练习俯卧撑 小兄弟 - 好吧
- Do your push-ups, brother. - All right.{
}
靠
Oh, fuck.{
}
战羊 有阵子没来咯
Ram man! Been a while.{
}
是啊 我刚在附近转转 就想着跟你出去吃点东西
Yeah, I was in the neighborhood, thought maybe we could go grab a...a hamburger.{
}
我在工作呢
I'm working.{
}
好吧 晚些吧
Okay. You know, maybe later.{
}
你没事吧？
You okay?{
}
- 能跟我聊几句吗？ - 当然
- Could we talk for a second? - Sure.{
}
当然 怎么了？出了什么事？
Sure. What's up? What's up?{
}
我是想找个安静地方…
No, I mean somewhere quiet, not...{
}
兰迪
Randy...{
}
我不能扔下客人不管 你知道的
I can't leave with a customer, you know.{
}
听我说 我不久前心脏病发
Listen. I had a heart attack.{
}
我明白
I know.{
}
- 你车停哪？ - 停在后门
- Where you parked? - Out in the back.{
}
好 你先上车 我过15分钟就来找你
Good. Go to your car. I'll meet you out there in 15 minutes.{
}
哦 他们只是干爱 还是还干了些别的？
So, they're just fucking, or what's the story?{
}
我…我休息一下
You know what? I'm gonna...I'm gonna go on break.{
}
- 我得找根烟抽 真是戒不掉 - 好吧
- I need a cigarette. I can't quit. - Okay.{
}
- 嘿 - 多谢 我很感激
- Hey. - Thanks. I appreciate it.{
}
没什么
No, it's okay.{
}
- 什么时候发作的？ - 两个礼拜前
- When was it? - Uh, a couple weeks ago.{
}
你现在感觉如何？
Oh. How are you feeling?{
}
呵呵 没有大力士的神勇状态
Oh. I don't feel like Hercules.{
}
- 怎么回事？ - 我…
- What happened? - I just...{
}
我在更衣室里走着走着 就突然像砖块一样砸在地上
I was walking in the dressing room, and the guys told me I just...{
}
这是一个伙计事后告诉我的 我什么都不记得了
dropped like a brick, and, you know, I don't remember nothin'{
}
现在医生告诉我…
Now the doctors tell me, uh...{
}
说我再也不能…
that I can't...{
}
再也不能摔角了
that I can't wrestle no more.{
}
那你打算怎么办？
What are you gonna do?{
}
你知道吗 我就感觉哪不对劲似的
You know, it just don't feel... right.{
}
所以…
And that's why...{
}
我特想跟你聊聊
That's why I wanted to talk to you, you know.{
}
因为我不想一个人呆着
'Cause I don't want to be alone.{
}
兰迪
Randy.{
}
这样的时候 你应该跟你的家人在一起
You should be with your family now.{
}
你不是有女儿吗？她在哪？
Don't you have a daughter? Where's your daughter?{
}
我女儿… 她不喜欢我
Uh, my daughter...she don't like me very much.{
}
我才不信 每个人都需要父亲
I don't believe it. Everybody needs a father...{
}
而且 相信我
and... trust me...{
}
这样的事总是能把家人团结在一起
this kind of thing brings people together.{
}
你应该给她打电话
You should call her.{
}
我得回去了
I should go back in.{
}
你会好好的 对吧？
You're gonna be okay, huh?{
}
- 我没事 - 那就好
- I'll be okay. - Okay.{
}
斯蒂芬妮
Stephanie.{
}
你好 我是斯蒂芬妮 请留言
Hi, this is Stephanie. Leave a message.{
}
老天
Man.{
}
哦 请问 斯蒂芬妮在家吗？
Oh. Uh, is, uh, Stephanie home?{
}
- 你哪位？ - 呃 我是她爸爸
- Who can I say it is? - Uh, tell her it's her father.{
}
嘿 斯蒂芬妮
Hey. Stephanie.{
}
- 你去哪里？ - 你想怎样？
- Where you goin'? - What do you want?{
}
呃 我只是 我只是想跟你谈谈
Well, I just- I have to talk to you.{
}
我现在没时间
I can't really talk right now.{
}
- 我真的必须跟你谈谈 - 我得上学去
- I really need to talk to you. - I have school.{
}
- 你在上学？ - 是啊
- You're going to school? - Yeah.{
}
哦 真好
Well, that's great.{
}
听我说 我心脏病发作…
Listen. I had a heart attack...{
}
所以我觉得有必要告诉你
and I just thought I needed to tell you.{
}
你真是个混蛋
You are such an asshole.{
}
你到底打什么主意？
What do you want from me?{
}
你要怎样？
What do you want?{
}
我只是…很孤独
I just been alone, and, uh...{
}
而你是我女儿 我爱你 我想见你
you're my daughter, and I love you, and I just...I just needed to see you.{
}
屁话
That's bullshit.{
}
你只是想要我照顾你
You want me to take care of you.{
}
- 不是的 - 就是!
- No. - Yes.{
}
你想都别想
Well, I'm not gonna do that.{
}
我需要你照顾的时候 你他妈的在哪？
'Cause where the fuck were you when I needed you to take care of me?{
}
这么多年来
You know, on all my birthdays...{
}
你从来没为我庆祝过生日
which you never even made one.{
}
你可能都不知道我生日是哪天
You probably don't even know when it is.{
}
所以 你心脏病发关我屁事！操你妈！
So, you know what? No. I don't care if you had a heart attack. Fuck you!{
}
- 哎 战羊 - 嘿
- Oh! Ram. - Hey.{
}
- 没想到在这里碰到你 - 为什么
- Didn't think I'd see you here. - Why not?{
}
- 嘿 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.{
}
我听说你在迪夫索表演之后晕倒了
I heard you collapsed at the DiFusco show.{
}
哦 只是玩的过火 接不上气
Ah, man, I just overheated and blacked out. That's all.{
}
- 真的吗？ - 是啊 在医院呆了不到一个小时就出来了
- Really? - Yeah, I was out of the hospital in less than an hour.{
}
- 那你没事了？ - 兄弟 我整装待发
- So, you're fine? - Brother, I'm good to go.{
}
太好了 我还准备取消小旅行车呢
That's excellent! I was just gonna cancel the minivan.{
}
- 什么小旅行车？ - 我租了一辆准备去观看你们重战
- What minivan? - I rented one for Fanfest.{
}
我们整个亲友团一起去
Yeah, m-me and the whole gang's driving down.{
}
特里 加利亚诺 “肥背”
Terry C., Caggiano, Fatback.{
}
我真是要乐疯了
Oh, I'm so fucking psyched!{
}
沃派还给了我好多传单
Volpe gave me an assload offlyers.{
}
太好了 到时候肯定史诗级的
Yeah. It's gonna be epic.{
}
沃派还说我们这里的人都会去观战
Volpe said the scout from the show was gonna be there.{
}
二十年打造的重战
Twenty years in the making.{
}
- 会让人记住的 - 来吧 你的东西我都摆好了
- It's gonna be something. - Yeah. Come on. I got you set up down here.{
}
- 嘿 兄弟 - 嘿 怎么样 兄弟
- Hey, bro. - Hey. What's going on, bro?{
}
嗯 看来今天能来不少人
So, uh, yeah. Should get a pretty good crowd today.{
}
哦 太好了 我先活动活动手指
Oh. Great. I'll, uh- I'll loosen up.{
}
好的
All right.{
}
嘿 大个子 你近来可好？真高兴见到你
Hey, my man. How you doing, big guy? Good to see you. Wow.{
}
很久不见
Haven't seen you in a while.{
}
- 笑一个 - 你这T恤哪定做的？
- Smile. - Who makes your T-shirts?{
}
你这T恤不错
I like your T-shirts.{
}
- 签名照多少钱？ - 10块
- How much for an autograph? - Ten dollars.{
}
- 战羊 我崇拜你好多年了 - 嘿 怎么样 老兄
- Ram. Been a big fan of yours for years. - Hey. How you doin', brother?{
}
- 能见到你真是太好了 能合照一张拍立得吗？ - 没问题
- It's really great to meet you. Can I get a Polaroid? - All right. Absolutely.{
}
准备好了吗 大家？
Okay. Ready, guys?{
}
战羊！
Ram!{
}
- 你叫什么名字来着？ - 埃文
- What's your name again? - Evan.{
}
- 埃文  E- E-V- - E-V-A-N.
- Evan. E- E-V...  - E-V-A-N.{
}
- 1 2 战羊 - 好了
- One, two, Ram! - There we go.{
}
八块钱 这个给你 马修
Okay, it's eight. There you go, Matthew.{
}
给你
- Here you go. - Yeah, hold on.{
}
不对 是30块
Well, no. It's $30.{
}
一定得买录影带 我给你拿录像带
You gotta get the VHS. I'll give you the VHS.{
}
嘿 我是卡斯蒂
Hi, I'm Cassidy.{
}
- 我叫亨利 - 很高兴见到你 你从哪来？
- Henry. - Nice to meet you. Where you from?{
}
- 加菲尔德 - 哦？
- Garfield. - Yeah?{
}
你今晚玩得可好？
How you doing tonight?{
}
还行
- Okay. - Mm-hmm?{
}
给你单独跳一个怎么样？ 让你更爽
How about a private dance, make you feel a little better?{
}
- 呃 不用了 - 真的不用？亨利？
- Mmm, no, not tonight. - No, Henry?{
}
- 不用 - 不用？好吧
- No. - No? Okay.{
}
别忘了 周二之夜是属于…
And don't forget Tuesday night is...{
}
# Is how you dance You're up to no- #{
不用
Nah.{
}
是我们别有风味的…
On the main stage, the exotic...{
}
嘿 你好
Hey. Hey, you.{
}
嘿 你什么时候来的？
Hey. When'd you get here?{
}
- 刚来 - 是吗？
- I just flew in. - You did?{
}
- 最近身体怎么样？ - 感觉很好
- How you been feeling? - I'm feeling good.{
}
- 好多了 - 那就好
- A lot better. - Good.{
}
还有 我采纳了你的意见 去看了我女儿
And I took your advice. I went and saw my daughter.{
}
是吗？怎么样？
Yeah? How did that go?{
}
呃 不怎么好…
Uh, it didn't go very well.{
}
她把我骂的狗血淋头
She sort of ripped me a new asshole.{
}
啊 很抱歉
Oh. Oh. Sorry to hear that.{
}
呵呵 还能怎么办
Oh, hey. What are you gonna do?{
}
只是…
Oh, just...{
}
如果我能为她做点什么特别的 也许…
Maybe if I went out and did something special, you know?{
}
- 给她买个礼物 - 这个主意好！
- Bought her a present. - That's a really great idea.{
}
- 不过… - 她喜欢什么？
- Well... - What's she into?{
}
呃 我真的…你也知道…
Hmm. Yeah, I don't really- You know.{
}
她喜欢什么类型的音乐？
What kind of music does she like?{
}
我真的不知道
I really don't know.{
}
那她喜欢别的什么吗？ 烹调或者阅读？
Well, is she into something else, like, well, cooking or books or something?{
}
- 我不知道 - 好吧…
- I don't know. - Okay. Well...{
}
你可以给她买衣服 小女孩的衣服
you should get her clothes, like some kind of clothes.{
}
- 女孩很受用的 - 真的？
- All girls like that. Yeah. - Yeah?{
}
- 嗯 听起来不错 - 我知道一个好地方
- Okay. Sounds good. - Hey. I know the right place.{
}
在伊丽莎白 有个超赞的复古服饰店
It's this kick-ass little vintage shop in Elizabeth.{
}
- 呃 - 应该是在伊丽莎白道
- Ah. - I think it's on Elizabeth Avenue.{
}
周六去最好 因为他们每周六上新货
You should go on Saturday. That's when they get all the best shit.{
}
谢谢你 真的多谢
Hey, thanks. Thanks a lot.{
}
我给你跳个舞？
You want a dance?{
}
我的身体可能还没恢复到那个程度
I don't think I'm quite ready for that yet.{
}
好吧
Okay.{
}
# We about to blow, oh #{
# Now they callin'me Hollywood #{
}
# Say what you want, hater It's all good, yeah #{
# No matter where I go I can represent hood #{
}
呵呵 动作真快
Well, that was fast.{
}
不如我们周六在那家店见？
Listen. Why don't I meet you there on Saturday...{
}
我可以帮你选衣服
and, um...and help you pick something out?{
}
哇 太好了
- Wow. I'd like that a lot. - Oh.{
}
- 1点？ - 好
- 1:00? - Yeah.{
}
- 好 - 1点
- All right. - 1:00.{
}
嗯 1点
Yeah, 1:00.{
}
嘿 哇…
Hey. Whoa.{
}
你不记得怎么敲门了么？
Did you forget how to knock?{
}
- 不是的 - 从头来过 我说真的
- No. - Let's try that again, all right? I'm serious.{
}
你要干嘛？
What do you want?{
}
嗯 我想…能不能在这里…
Well, I was wondering if I could get some more work- something, uh...{
}
- 干个稳定的全职工作 - 呃 手机忘了
- you know, steady, full-time. - Ah, cell phone.{
}
现在只有周末的班有空缺
All I got is weekends.{
}
没问题
Yeah, well, that works.{
}
周末你不是要去拿屁股砸人脸么？
Isn't that when you sit on other dudes' faces?{
}
- 说吧 有什么工给我做 - 熟食柜台
- So, what do you got? - Deli counter.{
}
- 熟食柜台？要跟顾客打交道之类？ - 是
- Deli counter. Dealing with the customers and stuff? - Yeah.{
}
热辣又性欲高涨的主妇们接踵而来
A parade of hot, horny housewives...{
}
贪恋乞讨你的肉
begging for your meat.{
}
- 还有别的工作吗？ - 没有了
- You got anything else? - No, I do not.{
}
想不想干？
You interested?{
}
当然
Yeah. Sure.{
}
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey! - Hey.{
}
老天 我几乎认不出你了
Goddamn. I almost didn't recognize you.{
}
你…你看起来干净多了
You look...You look clean.{
}
干净？
Clean?{
}
不是 我想说的是你看起来很美
No, I mean you look lovely.{
}
好吧 谢谢
Okay. Thanks.{
}
嗯 我该叫你帕米还是卡斯蒂？
Uh, listen. Should I call you, uh, Pam or Cassidy or what?{
}
- 帕米 - 好 帕米
- Pam. - Pam.{
}
别叫太顺口就好
Don't get used to it.{
}
她穿什么风格？
What is she?{
}
黑色高特风？朋克风还是嘻皮风？
Goth? Punk? Hippie?{
}
- 还是大学校园风？ - 哦 老天 我完全不明白
- Preppy? - Oh, man, I ain't got a clue.{
}
嘿 帕米
Oh. Hey, Pam.{
}
- 帕米 - 嗯？
- Pam. - Yeah. Mm-hmm?{
}
谢谢你 我真的很感激
Thank you. I really appreciate this.{
}
不用谢
You're welcome.{
}
嗯 我想说…
Uh, listen.{
}
我觉得斯蒂芬妮
I think Stephanie is, uh...{
}
是同性恋
a lesbian.{
}
阿？
Uh-huh?{
}
这对她穿什么风格有影响么？
Does that make a difference what she...{
}
没有
No.{
}
- 没关系的 - 我想可能是我自己想太多 我也不知道
- It's cool. - I mean, or maybe it's all in my head. I don't know.{
}
哇 这个不错哦
Oh, wow. What about this?{
}
看 上面有个“s” （斯蒂芬妮首字母）
Look at this. Got an "S" on it.{
}
非常适合对吧？
- Um... - That looks perfect, huh?{
}
呃…
Well...{
}
现在是冬天 还是给她买个厚点的比较好 比如这件短大衣
I mean, it's winter, so maybe you want something warmer, like a peacoat.{
}
有道理
You got a point there.{
}
- 如果你知道她的尺寸 - 嗯 这个真的不错
- If you know her size. - Yeah, that's pretty cool.{
}
我就觉得… 看起来很摇滚
I don't know, man. I think that's pretty rock and roll.{
}
你觉得怎么样？
- What do you think? - I...{
}
跟着感觉走吧
You should go with your gut, man.{
}
- 真的？ - 嗯
- Yeah? - Yeah.{
}
你在天光里看起来真的美极了
You know, you look so goddamn pretty in the daytime.{
}
跟我去喝一杯怎么样？
Hey, have a beer with me?{
}
我得走了
Uh, I gotta get going.{
}
- 就喝一杯 - 我真的…
- One beer. - I really...{
}
我…我有个孩子
I got a...I got a kid.{
}
你有孩子？
You have a kid?{
}
嗯…
Well.{
}
- 男孩还是女孩？ - 男孩 叫杰姆森
- What do you have, a boy or girl? - Boy. Jameson.{
}
- 几岁了？ - 9岁
- So, how old? - Nine.{
}
哇 真是看不出来
Wow. Hmm. Who would figure, huh?{
}
我一般不跟客人说这些的
Well, it's not something I usually tell the customers.{
}
说这个可不会让他们想买我跳舞
It's not exactly...It's not a turn-on.{
}
哦 等等
Uh, hold on. Wait a second.{
}
你把这个给你的小家伙
I want you to give this to your little guy. It's a...{
}
这是战羊小人偶
It's a Randy the Ram action figure.{
}
叫他好好保存 值300块钱呢
Tell him not to lose it. It's a $300 collector's item.{
}
- 真的？ - 没有啦
- Really? - No.{
}
来吧 就一杯
Come on. Hey, one beer.{
}
好吧
Okay.{
}
你儿子长得很漂亮
That's a great-looking kid you got there.{
}
我也觉得
I think so.{
}
看看他妈妈就知道为什么他长得好看啦
Well, I can see where he got his good looks from.{
}
呵呵 他的确没遗传他爸的外表
Yeah. Well, he doesn't get it from his father.{
}
这是什么？
What's that?{
}
这个是特林顿的公寓
Oh, that's this condo thing down in Trenton.{
}
你是打算搬去那住？
What are you thinking about, moving there?{
}
- 计划中 - 真的？
- Workin' on it. Yeah. - Yeah?{
}
嗯 那里的学校超一流的
Mm-hmm. Yeah, the schools are really awesome...{
}
社区也好 价钱又便宜
great neighborhood, and... cheaper.{
}
那你在“绮桂斯”的表演怎么办？
What about your gig over at, uh, Cheeques?{
}
不干了呗
Done. Quitting.{
}
- 哇… - 没错
- Oh, wow. - Yeah.{
}
哦 哈哈…
Whoa! Hell, yeah!{
}
太好了 来吧宝贝
All right! Come on, baby.{
}
- 跟我跳一曲 - 在这儿？
- Dance with me. - Here?{
}
对阿 就在这儿
- Yeah, right here. Come on. - Uh-uh.{
}
- 来吧 - 这首我跳的太多次了
- Come on. - l-I've danced to this plenty.{
}
好吧 我给你跳好了 欣赏吧
Okay. I'll dance for you then. Here we go.{
}
# That's where we meet #{
- 我们轮班好了 - 嘿嘿 我正需要个工作呢
- Think I can get you a shift. - Hey, man, I need a job.{
}
说定了
There we go.{
}
哦 原来你是给我跳艳舞呢
Ooh! It's a lap dance I'm getting.{
}
# I knew right from the beginning #{
# That you would end up winning #{
}
# I knew right from the start #{
# You'd put an arrow #{
}
# Through my heart #{
# Round and round #{
}
靠 版本不一样了
Yeah! Goddamn, they don't make 'em like they used to.{
}
- 他妈的80年代音乐 最赞的 - 说得好
- Fuckin' '80s, man. Best shit ever. - Bet your ass, man.{
}
- 枪炮与玫瑰他妈的神了 - 没话说
- Guns N' Roses fuckin' rules. - Crol.{
}
- 没错 - 还有戴夫·来帕德
- Yeah. - Def Lep.{
}
这一切都给那个叫科本的贱逼给搞砸了 （科特·科本 涅磐乐队主唱）
Then that Cobain pussy had to come around and ruin it all.{
}
好像痛快玩一场有罪似的
Like there's something wrong with wanting to have a good time.{
}
我告诉你吧 我就烦90年代音乐
I'll tell you something. I hated the fuckin' '90s.{
}
- 他妈的90年代音乐真烂 - 90年代音乐真他妈的烂
- Nineties fuckin' sucked. - Nineties fuckin' sucked.{
}
- 操 - 怎么了？
- Shit. - What's the matter?{
}
不能跟客人场外联系 我得走了
No contact with the customers. I gotta go.{
}
嘿 你说了 要喝一杯的
Hey. You said one beer.{
}
- 有说吗？ - 对阿
- I did? - Yeah.{
}
哦 好吧
Oh, okay.{
}
# I knew right from the beginning #{
# That you would end up winning #{
}
# I knew right #{
一杯酒
- # From the start # - One beer.{
}
# You'd put an arrow through my heart #{
# Round #{
}
喝完了
Here you go.{
}
嘿 兄弟 我的胸牌上的名字怎么不是“兰迪”？
Hey, bro. This is supposed to say "Randy."{
}
他们大概是从你社保单上抄下来的
I guess they got it off your W-4 or something.{
}
我真的要挂这个？
So I really gotta wear one of these things?{
}
不用 你与众不同
No, you're special.{
}
嗯 那你能不能帮我改一下名字？
Well, uh, can you change it?{
}
给你什么就挂什么 知道么？
Just wear the fuckin' thing, all right?{
}
操
Oh, fuck.{
}
这是你要的大红肠
Uh, here's your bologna, pal.{
}
18号
Eighteen.{
}
所有的都特价还是只有中号的特价？
Are-Are they all on sale, or just the regular ones?{
}
- 只有哈德森的特价 - 那应该标清楚啊
- The Hudson Acres. Uh- - Well, it wasn't very clear.{
}
- 我去给你查一下 - 好吧
- Let me check. - Okay.{
}
韦恩 请来熟食柜台
Wayne, to the deli counter.{
}
马上就好
It'll just be a minute.{
}
好吧 那你觉得那种熏肉最好？
Okay. So, uh, which, in your opinion, is the best smoked ham?{
}
- 什么最好？ - 熏肉
- The best what? - Smoked ham.{
}
- 呃… - 哪一种？
- Uh... - Which?{
}
我不… 熏肉阿…
I don't - Smoked ham, I guess-{
}
我看枫糖的不错
Uh, the maple-glazed is not bad.{
}
- 我要鸡胸跟鸡腿 - 鸡胸和鸡腿
- Breasts, thighs. - Breasts, thighs.{
}
- 小块的 - 好的
- Small pieces. - Right.{
}
- 先锁定 然后按“开始” - 好
- Lock it up. Push start. - Yes.{
}
46号
Forty-six.{
}
- 想要点什么？ - 我想要半磅蒜香意大利面沙拉
- What would you like? - Can I have a half a pound of pesto pasta salad?{
}
这就来
Okay. Comin' up.{
}
半磅蒜香意大利面来喽
Half a pound of pesto pasta on the button.{
}
- 还需要什么别的？ - 不用了
- Can I get you anything else? - No, that's it.{
}
- 祝你愉快 - 谢谢 你也是
- You have a lovely day, darling. - Thanks. You too.{
}
47号
Forty-seven.{
}
- 给我8块鸡 - 什么类型的鸡？
- Let me get a eight-piece, uh, chicken. - What kind of chicken you want?{
}
八块鸡 给我两个鸡胸
I want a eight-piece. That's two breasts.{
}
- 来两块大的 - 两块大鸡胸 这就来
- Give me two big breasts. - Two big breasts, coming up.{
}
就是这个 两块大鸡胸
That's what I want. Two big breasts.{
}
两个大（鸡）胸 希望不是胸大无脑
Two big breasts- Uh, something with a brain.{
}
- 还要两个翅膀 不要大腿 - 嗯
- And two wings? Yeah, stay away from them thighs. - Yeah.{
}
好多鸡就这么一去不返咯 祝你愉快
A lot of chicken flying out the door. There you go, honey. Have a good day.{
}
- 谢谢 也祝你愉快 - 下一位
- Thank you. Have a good day. - Who's next?{
}
- 我 - 想要什么 帅哥
- Me. - What you having, good-looking?{
}
- 半磅鸡蛋沙拉 - 半磅鸡蛋沙拉 这就来
- Uh, half a pound of egg salad. - Half a pound of egg salad, coming up.{
}
- 给你 - 新鲜吗？
- Here we go. - Fresh?{
}
- 新鲜？鲜嫩出炉的 老兄 - 好吧
- Fresh? Fresh as monkey's breath, brother. - Yeah.{
}
这个很不错的
Oh, yeah. This is the good stuff.{
}
来了 要输球了 来吧！
Comin' up. Down and out. Come on.{
}
最后一节 加油加油！（指的是美国橄榄球赛 假装自己在掷橄榄球）
It's the fourth quarter. Come on. Come on. Come on.{
}
最后十二秒 球来了！要输球了！双手接！
There's 12 seconds left. Go. Down and out. Here. Both hands.{
}
哈哈 触地得分！ 干的漂亮！
Hey! Touchdown! Goddamn! How about them Cowboys?{
}
- 你想要点什么 靓女？ - 嘿
- What you having, spring chicken? - Hi.{
}
- 嘿 米格 你好 - 哪位？
- Hey, Migg, how you doing? - Who is this?{
}
- 我是战羊 - 嘿 战羊 真高兴 我们两个礼拜之后就见面了
- Yeah, it's the Ram. - Hey, Ram. Good to hear from you. We gonna see you in two weeks?{
}
- 一定的 一定 - 肯定很火 已经有12个人给我打电话了
- Yeah, sure. Yeah. Yeah. - It's gonna be big. I got 12 calls already.{
}
听着 我不能参加尤蒂卡的表演了
Listen, uh, you're gonna have to count me out of Utica.{
}
什么意思？我票都卖了一个礼拜了
What do you mean? We've been selling tickets for a week!{
}
不行了 我退休了
Nah, I'm retiring.{
}
- 嘿 法兰克 你好 - 我很好 战羊 你怎么样？
- Hey, Frank, how you doin' - Good, Ram. Good. How are you?{
}
我很好 不过 听我说
Nah, I'm good, man. I'm good. Uh, listen.{
}
别这样啊 沃派 对不起 我做梦都想打
Oh, come on. I'm sorry, Volpe. You know I'd kill to do it.{
}
- 连鲍勃的机票我都买了 - 不 我知道 我了解
- I already bought Bob's plane ticket. - No, I realize. I understand.{
}
- 我觉得你以后会很后悔这个决定的 - 不 不会的 再也不打了
- I think you're making a big mistake. - Nah, no more. I am done.{
}
- 我退休了 - 嗯 我知道
- I'm retired. - Yeah, I-I-I know.{
}
斯蒂芬妮
Stephanie.{
}
你干吗？跟踪我？
What, are you stalking me?{
}
不 我只是给你买了个礼物
No. I, uh, brought you a present.{
}
打开看看
Go ahead. Open it.{
}
这上面的“S”代表你的名字
The "S" stands for "Stephanie."{
}
哦
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah.{
}
喜欢吗？
Do you like it?{
}
有点…太亮了点
It's, uh- It's shiny.{
}
这不是礼物 真正的礼物在后头
That's not really your present. I got you something else.{
}
等着
Hold on.{
}
这才是你的礼物
This is your real present.{
}
- 一件短大衣 - 现在是冬天…
- It's a peacoat. - Yeah. Well, it's wintertime...{
}
我希望你能穿的暖和
and I want you to keep warm.{
}
- 谢谢 - 一切为了你 孩子
- Thank you. - Hey, anything for you, sweetheart.{
}
嗯 你现在打算做什么？
So what are you doing right now?{
}
我打算做什么？
What am I doing?{
}
我是想 我们可以去我们最喜欢的地方
You know, I thought maybe we could, you know, stop by our old favorite place.{
}
我们有这样的地方么？
We have an old favorite place?{
}
到了那里你就知道了
You'll recognize it when you see it.{
}
现在不行
Uh, now's not really the best time. I...{
}
我有事要做
I got some stuff I gotta do.{
}
什么事？
What kind of stuff?{
}
就是有事
Just stuff.{
}
别这样 我又不会…
Come on. I'm not gonna, like...{
}
又不会咬你
I'm not gonna take a bite out of you or anything.{
}
只是想跟你多呆一会儿
Just, you know, hang out for a little while.{
}
我好久好久没来了
I haven't been here in ages.{
}
记得奇趣屋吗？
You remember the fun house?{
}
就在那儿 过去是“野兽旅馆”
Right there. Used to be the Monster Motel.{
}
- 差不多吧 - 你过去好喜欢的
- Kinda. - Oh, you loved it.{
}
我们还进去过 他们那些吓人的骷髅
We used to go in there, and they had this, uh, spooky-ass skeleton.{
}
会突然从棺材里跳出来
It would pop out of a coffin.{
}
把你吓得大哭 还想要跑出来
You'd get really scared and cry and wanna run out.{
}
可是你又会求我再带你进去
And then- then you'd beg to go back in again.{
}
有点受虐狂呵呵
Oh. Always was a glutton for punishment.{
}
你总是要坐在我腿上 不然你就不肯进去
Yeah, you wouldn't go in unless you could sit on my foot...{
}
然后你还环抱我的腿
and wrap your arms around my leg.{
}
我们就那样一路走下去
And we'd walk all the way through like that.{
}
我一点也不记得呢
Ah, I don't even remember that.{
}
我记得
I do.{
}
我只是想告诉你
I just want to tell you.{
}
我本应该
I'm the one...{
}
照顾一切的
who was supposed to take care of everything.{
}
把大家都照顾好
I'm the one who was supposed to make everything okay for everybody.{
}
事情却不是那样
But it just didn't work out like that.{
}
然后我走了
And I left.{
}
丢下你
I left you.{
}
完全不是你的错
You never did anything wrong.{
}
你知道吗 我曾经试着…
You know? I used to try to...{
}
忘记你
Huh! Forget about you.{
}
我曾经试着当作…
I used to try to pretend that...{
}
你根本不存在
you didn't exist.{
}
可我做不到
But I can't.{
}
你是我的女儿
You're my girl.{
}
你是我的…我的宝贝女儿
You're my little... You're my little girl.{
}
现在
And now...{
}
我老了 老成这堆烂肉
I'm an old, broken-down piece of meat.{
}
我只剩下我自己
And I'm alone.{
}
我知道我罪有应得
And I deserve to be all alone.{
}
我只是希望你不要恨我
I just don't want you to hate me.{
}
好吗？
Okay?{
}
嘿
Hey.{
}
老天 我们不能就这么进去
Oh, man, we can't go in there.{
}
来吧
Come on.{
}
天
Oh, God.{
}
- 哇… - 这里之前一定是个舞厅
- Whoo, man. Wow. - This must have been a ballroom or something.{
}
哦 看这个！ 我们可以…
Oh, look at this. We can...{
}
你看…
Hey, here we go.{
}
- 这是什么？ - 向你行礼阿
- What is that? - It's my bow to you.{
}
是不是我也该向你行礼？ 给你回礼？
Am I supposed to bow back? I bow to you?{
}
1 2 3…
One, two, three. One, two, three. One, two, three.{
}
你可以领跳 你跳的不错
You can lead. You're not bad.{
}
好吧 谢谢
Well, thank you.{
}
等等
Hold on.{
}
等等 让我给你开门
Wait. Let me get the door.{
}
我希望你没感到跟我一起出去太痛苦
Well, I hope that wasn't too painful for you.{
}
- 不会阿 不错 - 嗯…
- No, it was okay. - Yeah, well...{
}
好吧 再见
Okay, uh, bye.{
}
再见
Bye.{
}
我们可以一起去吃个饭什么的
Hey, maybe we could go out to dinner sometime.{
}
- 吃饭？ - 周五怎么样？
- Dinner? - You know, on Friday or something?{
}
你说了算
Whatever works for you.{
}
周六吧
Saturday would be better.{
}
- 周六？ - 嗯
- Saturday? - Yeah.{
}
没问题
You got it.{
}
嘿
Hey, you there. Hey.{
}
打开看看
Come on. Open it.{
}
我等一会儿人少了再打开吧
I'll wait till later when it's quiet.{
}
拜托 我想看你读它时候的表情
Oh, come on. I want to watch your face when you read it.{
}
谢谢 好甜蜜哦
Thank you. That's very sweet.{
}
真的 谢谢 你帮了我一个大忙
Hey, thank you. I mean, come on, baby. You saved my ass.{
}
什么？
What?{
}
我不能…这么做
I can't... do this.{
}
不能做什么？
Can't do what?{
}
这样
This.{
}
我以为我们之间有感觉
I thought we had a little something going on here.{
}
不是的 我是觉得你很好 你是个好人
No. W-Well- l- I think you're awesome. I think that you're a great guy.{
}
那还有什么问题呢？
So what's the problem?{
}
你以为我只是个脱衣舞娘
You think that I'm, like, this stripper, and I'm not.{
}
但我还是个妈妈
I'm a mom.{
}
我要负责任的 我有个儿子
I have responsibilities. I have a son.{
}
反正你不会想要一个拖油瓶
Anyway, you don't want that fuckin'luggage, so...{
}
如果我愿意呢？
What if I do?{
}
我不能这样做
I can't go there.{
}
- 那在酒吧那天怎么算？ - 那只能算是失误
- What about the other day? - It was a mistake.{
}
我可没觉得那是失误
It didn't feel like a mistake to me.{
}
舞厅归舞厅 真实生活归真实生活 不能混为一谈
The club and the real world- they don't mix.{
}
我告诉你 这都是废话连篇
I don't know. I'll tell you, I think that's a lot of bullshit...{
}
因为我觉得你对我有感觉
because I think you still feel something.{
}
你只是我的客人 我他妈的不能跟客人约会的
You're a customer, okay? You're a fucking customer. I don't go out with customers.{
}
明白没？
You got it?{
}
好吧 明白
Yeah, I got it.{
}
给我来点龙舌兰酒
Hey, can I have some tequila over here, please?{
}
好的
Sure.{
}
这样吧
I tell you what. Here.{
}
- 什么意思？ - 给我跳一个
- What's that? - I want a dance.{
}
别这样
Stop it.{
}
怎么了？有生意也不做吗？
What's the matter? You gonna refuse a paying customer?{
}
- 我他妈的就要你给我跳一个 - 操你妈
- I want a goddamn dance, sweetheart. - Fuck you!{
}
- 进去给我搔首弄姿吧你 - 滚！
- Get up there and move your ass. Squeeze your titties together. - Fuck off!{
}
- 扭屁股给我看！ - 操你妈！
- Shake your fucking ass... - Fuck you!{
}
- 战羊！ - 假装你喜欢我！
Ram! And pretend you like me!{
}
- 他妈的给我跳一个！ - 他妈的给我滚出去！
- Gimme a goddamn dance! - Get the fuck outta here!{
}
- 战羊 咱们出去说 - 我请你喝一杯 兄弟
- Ram! Let's take it outside. - Want a drink, my man?{
}
不用了
No, I'm okay.{
}
老天
Oh, God.{
}
- 战羊 老兄 怎么了？ - 嘿 拉里
- Ram! Hey, man. What's happening? - Hey, Larry.{
}
你过得还好吧？ 不是退休了吗 怎么还来这儿？
How ya doin' What are you doing here? I thought you retired.{
}
- 的确退休了 只是来看表演 - 哦 进来吧
- I did. I just came to see the show. - Well, come in.{
}
来吧 当然 快进去
Come on, man. Of course. Straight in.{
}
战羊！战羊！
Ram! Ram!{
}
嘿 怎么了 有段时间没见你了
Hey, what's up there? I haven't seen you for a while.{
}
都还好吧？
All good?{
}
好
Yeah!{
}
1 2 3…
One, two, three!{
}
- 嘿！ - 战羊！
- Hey! - Ram!{
}
- 你们表现真棒 - 怎么样 喜欢不？
- You guys were great. - What's up? Did you like it?{
}
- 很好 很精彩的表演 - 多谢 老兄
- Yeah, it was a hell of a show. - Appreciate it, man.{
}
- 你动作很快 很到位 - 多亏了他
- You were fast. You looked good. - 'Cause of this guy, man.{
}
- 还是多亏他 - 哎 关键是 观众喜欢你们
- Nah, 'cause of this guy.  - Hey. What's important...they liked you.{
}
- 说的对 - 他们看的过瘾
- Exactly. - They did. They loved it.{
}
- 你最近怎么样呢 老兄 - 呃 呆着呗
- So how you been, man? - Well, hanging and swinging, brother.{
}
- 那我们去喝几杯 - 你买单？
- You swing. I get a couple drinks. - Get a drink? You buying?{
}
- 我请 - 好啊
- I'll buy for you. - Yeah, you buying.{
}
一共50块
Fifty even.{
}
谢谢 枚丽斯
Oh. Thanks, Meliss.{
}
- 我认得你 - 哦 干杯
- You know, I know who you are. - Well, cheers.{
}
我哥哥把你的海报挂他房门上
My brother used to have your poster on his door.{
}
呵 你哥哥有品味
Well, your brother's got good taste.{
}
对 那张照片很惹火
Yeah, it was a pretty hot picture.{
}
你来我们这小地方做什么？
So, what are you doing in our town of Rahway?{
}
我们在集会中心有场表演
We did a show over at the rec center tonight.{
}
摔角 你还摔角呢？
Wrestling. Wow. So you still wrestle?{
}
- 还从栏绳顶跳下来么？ - 哦
- Still jumping off the top rope. - Oh, wow.{
}
那招很辣哦
That's hot.{
}
想不想high？
So, uh, do you want to party?{
}
high? 怎么个high法？
Party? What do you call party?{
}
不知道
I don't know.{
}
像救火员一样High
Party like a fireman party.{
}
操 很上劲
Oh, shit, that's speedy.{
}
他妈的怎么不去开房！
Oh, get a fucking room.{
}
哦 耶
Oh, yeah!{
}
哦 操
Oh, fuck.{
}
哦 天啊
Oh, God.{
}
妈的
Oh, shit.{
}
妈的…
Oh, sh- Oh, shit!{
}
操哦
Fuck!{
}
操他妈的
Goddamn it!{
}
呃 斯蒂芬妮在吗？
Hey, uh, is Stephanie home?{
}
斯蒂芬 看谁终于露脸了
Steph, guess who finally decided to show up.{
}
他就站在门口
Yeah, he's standing outside.{
}
不 我不想
No, I don't want to do that.{
}
我看你到你受苦 不想你再苦下去 我把这混蛋赶走吧
I've seen you get stressed out. I don't want you to be stressed. Let me get this asshole out.{
}
- 什么也别说 - 嘿
- Just don't, don't say anything. - Hey.{
}
- 谁让你进来了？ - 你进来干吗？
- Who said you could come in? - What are you doing in here?{
}
- 对不起 斯蒂芬妮 真的对不起 - 你他妈的给我滚出去！
- I'm sorry, Stephanie. I'm so sorry. - No, get the fuck out!{
}
- 我来处理 行吗？我能处理 - 能处理个屁
- I'm gonna handle this, okay? I can handle this. - Obviously not.{
}
- 我能搞定！ - 哦 别这样 我搞砸了 真的对不起
- I can handle this! - Oh, come on. I'm sorry I screwed this up.{
}
- 非常抱歉 - 别担心
- I'm so sorry. - Wait. Don't worry.{
}
- 我只是…你不用走… - 我会回来的
- I just... You don't have to leave. - I'll be back.{
}
操
Fuck.{
}
我在饭店等了两个小时! 他妈的整整俩小时！
I waited in that restaurant for two hours- Two fucking hours...{
}
一直跟自己说 可能他遇到什么事了 或者交通组阻塞
telling myself, " Maybe something happened. Maybe he's stuck in traffic."{
}
其实都不是！你只是重蹈覆辙！ 一而再 再而三！
But, no! You just keep doing the same shit to me over and over again!{
}
我知道 我真心道歉 我给你赔罪
I know, and I apologize. Look, I apologize.{
}
我脑子里千头万绪
I got a lot of stuff swimming around in my head...{
}
所以我就出去喝一杯 又喝了一杯 就不省人事了
and I went out and had a drink, and another drink, and I just spaced.{
}
- 烂到家了！ - 老天！我怎么可以这样对你？
- That is tough shit! - Goddamn it. Why do I do this to you?{
}
因为你是个人渣！
Because you are a fuck-up!{
}
你是个苟延残喘的人渣！
You're a living, breathing fuck-up...{
}
我他妈的再也受不了了！
and I cannot fucking do it anymore!{
}
我受不了了！我他妈的可不能为了你哭！ 我受不了了！
I can't stand it! I can't fucking cry for you! I can't fucking do it anymore!{
}
我他妈的…
I can't fucking...{
}
- 你真他妈的人渣！ - 冷静！别这样
- You are a fucking asshole! - Calm down. Stop.{
}
- 你这人渣！天杀的人渣！ - 冷静 冷静
- You are an asshole! You're a fucking asshole! - Calm down. Calm down.{
}
- 见鬼去吧！ - 冷静！冷静！
- Go fuck yourself! Go fuck... - Calm down. Calm down.{
}
- 别碰我！我恨你！ - 对不起 我明白
- Do not touch me! I fucking hate you! - I'm sorry. I know.{
}
- 我他妈的恨死你了！ - 我知道你恨我 我了解
- I fucking hate you! - I know you hate me. I know you do.{
}
我知道你恨我
I know you hate me.{
}
- 冷静 - 我告诉你吧！我一点也不在乎
- Calm down. - You know what? I don't care.{
}
我不恨你 也不爱你
I don't hate you. I don't love you.{
}
我也不喜欢你
I don't even like you.{
}
- 我真是太傻了 居然以为你会改变 - 我可以的…我可以改
- And I was stupid to think that you could change. - I can- I can change.{
}
- 我不在乎了 - 别这样
- I don't care. - Come on.{
}
没救了
There is no more fixing this.{
}
永久的完了
It's broke. Permanently.{
}
没什么不好的 其实更好
And I'm okay with that. It's better.{
}
对不起 真的真的对不起
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.{
}
我都不想再见你了
I don't ever want to see you again.{
}
看着我
Look at me.{
}
我不想看到你
I don't want to see you.{
}
不想听见你声音
I don't want to hear you.{
}
到此为止了
I am done.{
}
明白吗？到此为止
Do you understand? Done.{
}
出去
Get out.{
}
27号
Twenty-seven.{
}
请给我一磅德国土豆沙拉
Here. Apound of German potato salad, please.{
}
好的
Okay.{
}
少一点
A little less.{
}
再少一点
Less.{
}
少一点
A little less.{
}
多一点
A little more.{
}
多一点 再多一点
Little more, little more.{
}
好的
Okay.{
}
嘿 斯蒂夫
Hey, Stevie.{
}
多一点
A little more.{
}
少一点
A little less.{
}
再少一点
A little less.{
}
再少一点
Little less.{
}
给我1/4磅瑞士奶酪
Quarter pound of Swiss.{
}
再少一点
A little less.{
}
终于对了
At last.{
}
怎么回事 动作快点 现在是高峰时段
What's with the line? Let's pick things up. All right? It's rush hour.{
}
加油啊大家 动作快点 凯蒂呢？
Come on, people. Let's pick it up. Where's Katie?{
}
这儿呢
I'm here.{
}
哦 在这呢 忠于职守 很好哈
Oh, you're here. You're at your job. Great.{
}
祝您愉快 女士
Have a nice day, lady.{
}
快 快快
Go. Go, go, go.{
}
31号
Thirty-one.{
}
31号 我想要…
Thirty-one. Yeah, can I get...{
}
- 我们是不是在哪见过？ - 没有
- Do I know you from somewheres? - No.{
}
你看起来真的好眼熟
You just look so damn familiar.{
}
- 卡车工会的？ - 想要点什么？
- You Teamsters? - What are you having?{
}
给我半磅弗吉尼亚火腿
Uh, can I get a half-pound of Virginia ham...{
}
- 还有半磅带孔奶酪 - 好
- half-pound of the Jarlsberg? - Yeah.{
}
我肯定在哪见过你
I know I know you from someplace.{
}
我不知道
I don't know.{
}
- 你打垒球？ - 不打
- You play softball? - Nah.{
}
你不认识麦克·波士对吧？
And you're not one of Mikey Bosch's buddies, right?{
}
根本没听说过
Never heard of the guy.{
}
等等 你是战羊兰迪？
Wait a second. Randy the Ram?{
}
- 不是 - 80年代那个摔角手？
- No. - The wrestler from the '80s?{
}
- 战羊绝杀？ - 不是
- Ram Jam? - No.{
}
真诡异
That's freaky.{
}
- 你跟那人好像 - 是么？
- You look just like the dude. - Yeah?{
}
就是比他老
Except older.{
}
啊！见鬼！
Ah! Ah! Goddamn it!{
}
血！
Blood!{
}
兰迪 顾客都在这呢！
Randy- Randy, there are customers!{
}
- 你这小杂种！你还敢这样跟我说话？！ - 兰迪！
- You little prick! You gonna talk to me the way you do? Huh? - Randy!{
}
我他妈的不干了！
I fucking quit!{
}
- 我不干了 怎么着？ - 搞什么鬼 老大！
- I quit. All right? - What the fuck, man?{
}
要点见鬼的奶酪吗？娘们？
Want some fucking cheese, lady?{
}
- 你他妈的自己拿吧！ - 妈的疯子
- Huh? Get your own fucking cheese! - Fucking lunatic!{
}
- 操！ - 你疯了你！
- Oh, fuck! - Are you crazy?{
}
操 我他妈的不干了！
Ah, fuck! I quit!{
}
见鬼去吧 我不干了！
Goddamn it, I quit!{
}
老天 我不干了
God- I'm out of here!{
}
操
Ah, shit.{
}
操
Ah, fuck.{
}
哦 罗宾
Oh, Robin.{
}
罗宾 我的罗宾 不对 是兰迪 兰迪
Robin. Robin, man. It's Randy. Randy.{
}
- 听着 我打算干 - 你要干什么？
- Listen. I want to do it. - You want to do what?{
}
- 我要参加 那个特别活动 - 跟鲍勃打？
- I want back in. Fanfest. - With Bob?{
}
- 告诉他我回来了 - 可我请不起你了
- Just tell him it's back on. - I have no money to pay you.{
}
老兄 我可不在乎钱 我只想摔角
Hey, man, I don't give a shit. I just wanna wrestle. That's right.{
}
好的 说定了 兄弟
Okay. You got it, brother.{
}
# Too many slaves in this world #{
# Bondage is over the human race #{
}
# They believe slaves always lose #{
# And this fear keeps them down #{
}
# Watch the damned #{
# God bless ya #{
}
- # They're gonna break their chains # - # Hey #{
- # No, you can't stop them # - # God bless ya #{
}
# They're coming to get you #{
# And then you'll get your #{
}
- 他十一点之前必须上床 行么？ - 十一点
- I want him in bed by 11:00. - Okay.{
}
不能让他胡来
Yeah. I don't want him to bargain.{
}
再见 我的小猴子
Hey. Bye, monkey.{
}
跳回栏绳喽！ 把他翻下摔角台喽！
Bounce back on the ropes, flips him out to the stands!{
}
阿里站起来喽！ 踢他！
Ali gets back up, kicks him!{
}
踢！啊！哦！
Kick! Ah! Oh!{
}
1 2 3…你输了
One, two, three. You're out. Yea!{
}
嘿
Hi.{
}
嘿
Hey.{
}
你怎么知道我在这？
How'd you find me?{
}
- 大个子克里斯告诉我的 - 大个子克里斯？
- Big Chris. - Big Chris?{
}
- 绮桂斯的保安 - 哦 那个大个子克里斯
- Cheeques bouncer. - Right. Big Chris. Yeah.{
}
听我说 我那次突然像婊子似的跟你发飚 真对不起
Look, I'm...I'm...I know I came off like a bitch the other day, and I'm really sorry.{
}
我其实没想那样出口伤你 因为…
I didn't mean all those things that I said, 'cause...{
}
你对我来说 并不只是个客人
You're not just another customer.{
}
不过 话说回来 总有个界线…
But, you know, at the same time, I have this line...{
}
我不能…
and I just...{
}
- 逾越这个界限 - 我明白 别放心上
- I can't cross it. - No, I understand that. That's okay.{
}
- 我得走了 - 你去哪？
- I gotta go. - Where are you going?{
}
- 我有一场赛要打 - 比赛？
- I got a match. - A match?{
}
在惠明顿
It's in Wilmington.{
}
欢迎来观战
Come by.{
}
什么时候？什么比赛？
When is it? What?{
}
# Balls to the wall #{
# You'll get your balls to the wall #{
}
# Balls to the wall #{
# You'll get your balls to the wall #{
}
# Man #{
凤凰城绝不在话下
Phoenix is not out of the question.{
}
- 我还要把亚利桑纳拿下 明白？ - 看来是了
- I'm taking over Arizona. You hear me? - Looks like it.{
}
兰尼格朗！
Ram-a-lam!{
}
- 嘿 鲍勃 - 怎么样 老弟？
- Hey, Bob. - What's up, man?{
}
嘿 奈杰尔 久违了
Hey, Nigel. How you doing, brother? Long time.{
}
- 是啊 - 感觉还好吧？
- Yeah, man. - Feeling all right?{
}
- 嘿 看看 - 很高兴见到你 兄弟
- Yeah. Hey, look out. - Good to see you, bro.{
}
- 看看你 哇… - 你知道吗 我都没指望咱们能打这场了呢
- Yeah, look at you. Wow. - You know what? I didn't think we were gonna do this.{
}
我知道 大家都以为没戏了
Yeah. You and everybody else.{
}
周日晚上 他们打电话给我说 “他又回来了”
Sunday night, I get a call and they say, "He's back in. It's on again."{
}
我心想 “不是吧？”
I'm like, "What?"{
}
等你安顿下来 咱们谈谈比赛细节？
Listen, uh, when you get settled in, you want to go over some of the things?{
}
- 什么细节？ - 比赛战略
- What things? - Some of the spots.{
}
好的 这怎么样？我是恶人 你是正面人物 完了
Okay. How's this right here? I'm the heel and you're the face. Done.{
}
鲍勃 看到我们还跟过去一样 我很高兴
Hey, Bob. I'm glad to see things haven't changed.{
}
是啊 我也爱你
Yeah. I love you too.{
}
我们继续说 你想要什么车来着？
Now, back to you. Listen. What kind of car do you want, man?{
}
- 不知道 得我能买得起的吧 - 粉色的怎么样？
- I don't know. Uh, something affordable. - How about something pink?{
}
# You #{
# Get me loose #{
}
# I want ya #{
# That's all I do #{
}
# You #{
# Leave me loose #{
}
# I want ya #{
# That's all I do #{
}
# Make love to me right now #{
卡斯蒂 拜托 回来舞台上来吧
Cassidy. Come on, Cassidy. Get back up there.{
}
他们还没看够你呢
They're not done with you yet.{
}
你的鞋忘拿了
You left your shoes.{
}
卡斯蒂！卡斯蒂！
Cassidy. Cassidy!{
}
嘿 帕米
Hey, Pam!{
}
帕米
Pam.{
}
再往前三英里
Three more miles. Three more miles.{
}
体重252磅
Weighing in at 252 pounds...{
}
- 你真准备好打这一战了？ - 应该是吧
- You ready to do this thing? - I think so.{
}
- 中东野兽 - 场上见
- The Beast of the Middle East... - See you out there.{
}
阿亚图拉！
The Ayatollah!{
}
- 多少钱？多少钱？ - 20块
- Hey, hey, hey. How much? How much? How much? - Twenty dollars.{
}
后台怎么走？
Which way's backstage?{
}
这里就是后台？
This is backstage?{
}
他就是这么说的 呵？
That's what he said, huh?{
}
兰迪
Randy.{
}
- 嘿 - 哇 你来这里做什么？
- Hey. - Oh. What are you doing here?{
}
你他妈的上这来做什么？
What the fuck are you doing?{
}
干我的老本行呢 我正要开工
I'm doing my thing. I'm going to work.{
}
- 可是你的心脏… - 我的心脏？
- Yeah, but- but your heart. - My heart?{
}
我的心还跳着呢
My heart's still tickin'{
}
- 可是医生不是说… - 听着 我知道我在做什么
- Yeah, but the doctor said...  - Listen. I know what I'm doing.{
}
你知道吗 只有在那摔角场上 我才会受伤
And, you know, the only place I get hurt is out there.{
}
这个世界根本不管我死活
The world don't give a shit about me.{
}
我在这儿呢
I'm here.{
}
我就在这儿
I'm really here.{
}
- 这叫什么？ - U.S. A! U.S. A! U.S. A!
- What do you call that? - U.S.A! U.S.A! U.S.A!{
}
而他的对手 来自新泽西伊丽莎白
And his opponent, from Elizabeth, New Jersey weighing in at...{
}
体重225磅
- Hey. - 225 pounds{
}
- 你听到了吗？这才是属于我的地方 - 真正不朽的摔角传奇
- You hear them? This is where I belong. - a true wrestling immortal{
}
- 战羊 - 我得上场了
- Randy "The Ram"  - I gotta go.{
}
兰迪·罗宾逊
Robinson!{
}
不！不！兰迪 兰迪！
No, no, no. Randy! Randy!{
}
# She's got a smile that it seems to me #{
# Reminds me of childhood memories #{
}
# Where everything was as fresh as the bright blue sky #{
# Now and then when I see her face #{
}
# She takes me away to that special place #{
# And if I stare too long #{
}
# I'd probably break down and cry #{
# Whoa, whoa, whoa #{
}
# Sweet child o'mine #{
# Whoa, oh, oh, oh #{
}
# Sweet love of mine #{
我只是想…
I just want to say...{
}
对你们大家说…
to you all tonight...{
}
今晚 能站在这里 我心存感激
I'm very grateful to be here.{
}
很多人说我再也不会摔角了
A lot of people told me that I'd never wrestle again.{
}
而我毕生只为了摔角
And that's all I do.{
}
你努力活着 努力享乐
You know, if you live hard, and you play hard...{
}
- 你双倍的消耗着你的生命 - 我爱你 战羊
- and you burn the candle at both ends- - Love you, Ram!{
}
最终你就要付出代价
you pay the price for it.{
}
一辈子 你会失去你所珍爱的一切
You know, in this life you can lose everything that you love...{
}
以及所有珍爱你的人
and everything that loves you.{
}
现在我听力下降了
Now I don't hear as good as I used to...{
}
记忆力也衰退了
and I forget stuff...{
}
也不像过去那么帅了
and I ain't as pretty as I used to be.{
}
不过去他妈的 我还站在这里 我还是那个战羊
But goddamn it, I'm still standing here, and I'm the Ram.{
}
随着时间流逝
You know, as time goes by-{
}
随着时间流逝 有人会说 “他气数已尽”
as time goes by, they say, "He's washed up.{
}
“他玩完了 他不行了”
"He's finished. He's a loser.{
}
“他到头了”
He's all through."{
}
- 可是你们知道吗？ - 还有20年！
- But you know what? - Twenty more years!{
}
唯一能宣告我玩完了的人
The only ones who are gonna tell me when I'm through doing my thing...{
}
只有你们
is you people here.{
}
只有你们…
You people here- You people here are the ones...{
}
值得我战下去 你们就是我的家人
who are worth bringing it for, because you're my family.{
}
我爱你们！ 真心感谢你们！
I love all of you. Thank you so much!{
}
说的好 兰迪！
Great talk, Randy.{
}
谢谢
Thank you.{
}
把气氛炒起来 宝贝
Pick it up, baby.{
}
放轻松
Take it easy! Ah!{
}
- 你干什么呢？这是我的招！ - 打算放弃了？
- What are you doing? This is my move! - Giving up?{
}
你居然偷了我的招 兰迪？ 看我怎么使！
Steal my move, Randy? This is how you do it!{
}
这招得这么使！
This is how you do it!{
}
1 2…你以为你推谁呢！
One, two, th- Hey! Who you pushing?{
}
- 不用你告诉我该怎么做！ - 你胆敢推我！
- Do not tell me what to do! - You can't push me!{
}
不用你教！
Don't tell me!{
}
美国！美国！美国！
U.S.A! U.S.A! U.S.A!{
}
我几乎忘了这有多刺激了 兰迪！
I forgot how much fun this was, Ram!{
}
出招吧 鲍勃！
Bring it, Bob!{
}
人渣！来吧！
Asshole! Come on!{
}
你这邪教的！
Infidel!{
}
超神！超神！
Holy shit! Holy shit! Holy shit!{
}
嘿 你还好吧 裁判？
Hey, you okay, ref?{
}
现在就等我把你打趴下吧 宝贝
Now I'm gonna take you out, baby!{
}
美国！美国！美国！
U.S.A! U.S.A! U.S.A!{
}
完美谢幕吧
Let's take it home.{
}
兰迪 你没事吧？
Ram? Are you all right?{
}
你没事吧 战羊？
You okay, Ram?{
}
战羊？
Ram?{
}
现在由我来吧
I'll take it from here.{
}
钉住我！ 快点 钉吧！
Pin me! Come on, Ram. Pin me!{
}
我们给他们秀够了
We gave 'em enough.{
}
战羊 你还好吧？ 你没事吗？
Ram- Ram, you okay? You all right?{
}
没事了 战羊 收尾吧
It's okay, Ram. Take it home.{
}
战羊绝杀！战羊绝杀！
Ram Jam! Ram Jam! Ram Jam!{
}
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.{
}
# Have you ever seen a one-trick pony #{
# In the field so happy and free #{
}
# If you've ever seen a one-trick pony then you've seen me #{
# Have you ever seen a one-legged dog #{
}
# Makin'his way down the street #{
# If you've ever seen a one-legged dog then you've seen me #{
}
# Then you've seen me #{
# I come and stand at every door #{
}
# Then you've seen me #{
# I always leave with less than I had before #{
}
# Then you've seen me #{
# Bet I can make you smile when the blood it hits the floor #{
}
# Tell me, friend can you ask for anything more #{
# Tell me, can you ask for anything more #{
}
# Have you ever seen a scarecrow #{
# Filled with nothin' but dust and weeds #{
}
# If you've ever seen that scarecrow then you've seen me #{
# Have you ever seen a one-armed man #{
}
# Punchin'at nothin' but the breeze #{
# If you've ever seen a one-armed man then you've seen me #{
}
# Then you've seen me #{
# I come and stand at every door #{
}
# Then you've seen me #{
# I always leave with less than I had before #{
}
# Then you've seen me #{
# Bet I can make you smile when the blood it hits the floor #{
}
# Tell me, friend can you ask for anything more #{
# Tell me, can you ask for anything more #{
}
# These things that have comforted me I drive away #{
# This place that is my home I cannot stay #{
}
# My only faith's in the broken bones and bruises I display #{
# Have you ever seen a one-legged man #{
}
# Tryin'to dance his way free #{
# If you've ever seen a one-legged man then you've seen me #{
}